&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果我们不是在谈论Knowles和Undefined，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If we're not talking about Knowles and undefines, but
我们谈论的是字符串，数字和布尔值，这里有一种流行的感觉，
we're talking about strings, numbers and Booleans, there's a prevailing sense here,
从第四条到第七条，基本上，
from clauses four through seven, that essentially,
这个算法更喜欢做数值比较。
this algorithm prefers to do numeric comparison.
你会注意到四个不同的地方它叫两个号码。
You'll notice four different places it calls the two number.
它说如果类型X是数字，而另一个是字符串，
It says if the type X is number, but the other one is string,
然后调用字符串上的两个数字，这样我就可以进行数值比较。
then call two number on the string, so I can do a numeric comparison.
五个人都一样，六个人也一样。
Same thing in five, same thing in six.
如果其中一个是布尔值，那么对它做两个数字，并进行比较。
If one of them's Boolean, then do a two number on it, and make the comparison.
因此，它更愿意将所有内容简化为数字来进行比较。
So it prefers to reduce everything down to numbers to make the comparison.
现在你可能不喜欢算法就是这样工作的，但是
Now you may not like that that's the way the algorithm works, but
只要知道它能帮助你理解行为和
just by knowing that it helps you to understand the behaviors and
预测双等于算法的行为。
predict the behaviors of the double equals algorithm.
在某些情况下你认为发生了一件事，但是
That in some cases you thought one thing was happening, but
实际上，发生了一件完全不同的事情。
actually an entirely different thing was happening.
不是两个字符串进行比较，而是两个数字进行比较。
Instead of two strings getting compared, it's two numbers getting compared.
只是在你的脑后知道双等于更喜欢数字比较。
Just knowing in the back of your head double equals prefers numeric comparison.
有一个事实将您与99.99%的JavaScript开发人员区分开来，
That one fact separates you from 99.99% of all JavaScript developers,
因为他们从来没有读过说明书。
cuz they've never even read the spec.
那么，我们如何看待这种情况的发展呢？
So how do we see that playing out?
好吧，如果我有一个数字上的字符串，
Well, if I have a string on a number,
就像我在一号线上一样，这是一个数字，也是在线的，它是一个字符串。
like I am on line one, that's a number and online too, it's a string.
如果我做三倍等于，当然，我必须强制
If I do a triple equals, of course, I'm gonna have to forcibly make
要做比较的数字，它们必须是相同的类型。
the numbers to do a comparison, they're gonna have to be the same type.
如果我有一个三倍的等值，并且他们是不同的类型，它总是会失败。
If I had a triple equals and they were different types, it's always gonna fail.
所以我得做个数字。
So I'm gonna have to make numbers.
但如果我知道只能有数字或字符串，特别是如果其中一个是
But if I know there can only be number or string, especially if one of them is
绝对是一个数字，然后是一个完全相同的方式，就像我对最后一个数字所允许的那样
definitely a number, then an exactly the same way as I allow this with the last
东西签了，几面前，为什么不也允许和双等，
things sign, several sides ago, why not also allow with the double equals,
为什么不在网上说这个代码比较吵呢，不必要的这样
why not say that this code online for is more noisy unnecessarily so
双重等号的抽象在这里很有帮助。
and the abstraction of the double equals it's helpful here.
它说的是他们是一个数字还是
It's saying whether they're a number or
字符串，让它们相互比较。
a string, let's let them compare to each other.
如果他们是平等的，很好，如果不是，很好。
And if they're equal, great, and if not, great.
但是使用工具的抽象。
But use the abstraction of the tools.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我可以这样做，因为我设计了这个特定的功能
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I can do this because I designed this particular function or
这段特定的代码限制类型，
this particular piece of code to restrict the types,
说这里唯一可以考虑的类型
to say that the only types here that can be considered for
相等比较是字符串和数字。
the equality comparison are the string and the number.
如果我允许数组和
This would be a significantly more complex code if I would allow arrays and
物体和金条以及所有其他类型的东西来进行比较。
objects and bullions and all kinds of other types to come into that comparison.
所以我一直在做的案子是，
So the case that I keep making is,
您可以选择以这样一种方式来构造代码，即强制是一种有用的和
you can choose to structure your code in such a way that coercion is a useful and
明显的系统，而不是一些人感觉到的复杂魔术。
obvious system, rather than the complex magic that some people feel.
它把它带回合理和实用的领域
It brings it back within the realm of reasonable and practical for
您的代码基础。
your code basis.
不仅仅是为了你，而是为了你发展中的所有成员。
Not just for you, but for all the members of your development.
&GT；&GT；演讲者2：看，两种情况下的数字强度，它们都可能爆炸，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Look, numerical strengths in both cases, they could blow up,
他们不会吗？
wouldn't they?
这并不是两个数字的力量，就像论坛上的一样。
It wasn't both numerical strengths like from forum.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以如果它们都是字符串，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So if they were both strings,
让我们回到思考算法。
let's go back to thinking about the algorithm.
如果它们都是字符串，算法会做什么？
If both of them were strings, what does the algorithm do?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：传输号码。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Transmit the numbers.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：不，如果它们都是字符串，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Nope, if they are both strings,
这意味着它们都是同一类型的，那么算法做什么呢？
that means they are both of the same type, then what does the algorithm do?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：它做三重等于。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It does the triple equals.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它做三重等于。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It does the triple equals.
所以我对你的回应是，如果这些字符串是完全相同的，你就会得到真的，
So my response to you is, if those strings were literally identical, you'd get true,
否则你就不会。
and otherwise you wouldn't.
但你做的每一根弦都是一样的。
But that's the same for every string that you do.
你不能合理地期望一个字符串是3.7，一个字符串是。
You couldn't reasonably expect a string that said 3.7 and a string that said.
3.07为了彼此相等，这些字符串是相等的，这些数字是学习的。
3.07 to equal each other, those strings are equal and those numbers learn.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：就像一些输出基于它前面的表单输入一样，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Like a form input that some outputs base in front of it,
例如，它们变得很奇怪，但如果它是一个关于前面空间的数字。
for example, they become weird but if it's a number about the space in front.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：再次，让我们重新回到上下文，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Again, let's reset back to the context,
当类型不同时，双等号将允许强制。
the double equals is going to allow coercion when the types are different.
如果您所处的场景中的类型没有不同，
If you're in a scenario where the types are not different,
如果类型相同，则永远不会调用强制，永远不会。
where the types are the same, then it's not ever going to invoke coercion, ever.
如果你想要一些其他的行为，
If you want some other additional behavior,
你想要的不是强迫，
the thing that you want is not coercion here,
你想要的是字符串修剪，或者字符串格式化或类似的东西。
the thing you want is string trimming, or string formatting or something like that.
如果你有一个案例，你有两个字符串
If you have a case where you have two strings that could have
两边都有空格，你真的只关心中间的东西。
whitespace on either side, and you really only care about the stuff in between.
太好了，这就是所谓的字符串修剪。
Great, there's a thing for that and it's called string trimming.
但这不是强迫。
But that isn't coercion.
强制是当我有一个字符串和一个数字，并且
Coercion is when I have a string and a number, and
我希望这些可以互相比较。
I'd like those to be compared to each other.
这有帮助吗？
Does that help?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, yeah.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, all right.
所以回到我们的算法，最后一部分，类8和
So back to our algorithm, the final part, classes 8 and
9，如果您将双等号与还不是原语的内容一起使用，
9, if you use a double equals with something that's not already a primitive,
猜猜我们把我们的朋友召唤到了原始人身上。
guess what we invoke our friend to primitive.
我们调用两个原始抽象操作。
We invoke the two primitive abstract operation.
我们已经看过了。
We already looked at that.
记住，这是一个调用两个字符串或其他值的函数。
Remember that's the one that calls value over two string or whatever.
这里的要点是Double Equals只比较原语。
The takeaway here is that double equals only compares primitives.
如果你把它和不是原语的东西一起使用，它会做什么？
If you use it with something that's not a primitive, what's it gonna do?
把它变成原始物。
Turn it into a primitive.
只有当它们完全相同时，它才会对非原语执行某些操作
The only time it does something with non primitives is when they're the exact same
类型，然后它只做相同的值三重等于比较。
type and then it just does the same value triple equals comparison.
否则，它说，听着，
Otherwise, it says, listen,
我现在唯一关心的强制步骤就是让你成为一个原始人。
the only coercion step I care about right now is getting you to be a primitive.
然后我们将重新考虑基元是否是相同类型的。
And then we'll reconsider whether the primitives are at the same type or not.
还记得我之前在课程中说过的话吗？
Remember how I said earlier in the course,
这些算法在某种程度上是递归的。
that these algorithms are sorta inherently recursive.
双等于运算符说，我需要直截了当，
The double equals operator says, I need to get it to the point,
其中一个条款匹配。
where one of these clauses matches.
如果你给我一个不完全匹配的场景，
If you give me some scenario where it doesn't match completely,
然后我会一遍又一遍地运行算法
then I'm gonna re-run the algorithm over and over and
一遍又一遍，直到我把它归结为两个相同类型的基元。
over again, until I get it down to two primitives that are of the same type.
或者可以强制地彼此相等的两个原语。
Or two primitives that can be coercively equal to each other.
如果我永远都到不了那个点，你猜怎么着，假的，它们是不相等的。
And if I never get to that point, guess what, false, they are not equal.
换句话说，我们将调用两个原语并获得两个原语，然后
So in other words, we would invoke the two primitive and get two primitives, and
然后使用我们的两个原语返回算法，并且
then come back to the algorithm with our two primitives, and
然后做出相应的决定。
then make the decision accordingly.